[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following quote is from what 2003 comedy movie: You smell like beef and cheese.?", "correct_answer": "Elf", "incorrect_answers": ["Bad Santa", "Broken Arrow", "Tin Cup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All flamingos have 12 black flight feathers at the tips of each wing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What chemical is added to table salt in some European countries to prevent tooth decay?", "correct_answer": "Sodium fluoride", "incorrect_answers": ["Calcium sulfate", "Potassium carbonate", "Sodium nitrate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the alias James Bond uses in A View to a Kill, when he is at the villains French chateau in Chantilly?", "correct_answer": "Saint John Smythe", "incorrect_answers": ["Trumbull", "Gillespie", "Keating"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ben, the protagonist in the movie 21, is emotionally distracted one night and continues to play after being signaled to leave. How much does he lose?", "correct_answer": "$200,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$50,000", "$300,000", "$100,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie I Am Sam, when Sam and Lucy go to the school Halloween party, what is Sam dressed up as?", "correct_answer": "A Beatle", "incorrect_answers": ["Freddy", "A Baby", "Michael Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the strongest muscle in the body in relation to its size?", "correct_answer": "Masseter", "incorrect_answers": ["Deltoids", "Tongue", "Gluteus Maximus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What title does Blofeld claim in the film On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Count", "incorrect_answers": ["Duke", "Marquess", "Viscount"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1987 horror movie does this conversation occur:\n-Wait a minute, who am I here?\n-Jerry?\n-Thats right. Jerry Blake. Thanks, honey.?", "correct_answer": "The Stepfather", "incorrect_answers": ["American Gothic", "Shocker", "Brain Damage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who made the first chocolate bar?", "correct_answer": "J. S. Fry  Sons", "incorrect_answers": ["Nestle", "Mars", "Hershey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What weapon does Puss in Boots always carry around in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "Sword", "incorrect_answers": ["Knife", "Revolver", "Whip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which plant, that grows in the equatorial rainforests of Sumatra, Indonesia, has the largest unbranched inflorescence in the world?", "correct_answer": "Titan arum", "incorrect_answers": ["Rafflesia amoldii", "Talipot palm", "Tillandsia"]}]